w3links.net 2010-12-01

# Privacy Policy :: Free For All Links - Free submission - Link Directory

|  | 

The visitors (the "User") of the **W3links.net** websites are in control of the use of information they provide to **W3links.net,** or one of its current or future affiliate members ("Affiliate Members"). **W3links.net** is committed to respecting the privacy rights of Users to the **W3links.net** website (the "Site"). While visiting the Site, we may ask Users to provide personal information ("Personal Information") for purposes of interacting with the Site. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

Please see the Effective Date stated at the conclusion of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and dissemination of information that we collect from Users. To the extent that Users disclose any such information to other parties, through other web sites on the Internet linked to this site or otherwise, THIS PRIVACY POLICY SHALL NOT APPLY TO SUCH DISCLOSURE. Since **W3links.net** do not control the privacy policies of third parties, Users are subject to the privacy customs and policies, if any, of that third party, and **W3links.net** shall not be responsible for the use or dissemination of Personal Information by that third party. Therefore, we encourage Users to ask questions before they disclose Personal Information to other parties.

**Information Collected.**  
These websites automatically collect and/or tracks various information, including but not limited to (1) the home server domain names, e-mail addresses, type of client computer, and type of web browser used to access the Site; (2) the e-mail addresses of Users that communicate with us via e-mail, or users that posted messages to the MyEvent.com bulletin boards, or users that post messages to **W3links.net** chat groups; (3) Personal Information specifically provided by the User in online forms, registration forms, surveys, and contests entries, and (4) user-specific information on what pages Users access.

In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and/or create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. **W3links.net** store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at info@W3links.net to request that we remove this information from our database.

**W3links.net** is the sole owner of the information collected on **W3links.net**. These websites collect personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.  
**  
Use of Personal Information.**  
Information to Users.  
**W3links.net** reserves the right to use the Personal Information of Users to send them information via email about **W3links.net** , the Site, our products and services, and other topics or products, from theses websites or others, in which such Users may have indicated interest. If a User prefers not to receive such messages, he/she may send an e-mail message to info@W3links.net with the subject "unsubscribe". **W3links.net** reserves the right to contact Users regarding accounts status and changes to the Terms of Use Agreement, this Privacy Policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to the Site and/or to Users.  
**  
Data Analysis & Other User.**  
Personal Information collected by these websites either on a form or passively, will be used by **W3links.net** for general business purposes, including but not limited to editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of users' behavior, for product development, for content improvement, to inform advertisers as to how many Users have seen or clicked on their advertisements, and to customize content and layout of the Site.

**Sharing of Personal Information.**  
**W3links.net** will not sell, rent, swap, or otherwise disclose the registration data of Users to any unaffiliated third party. However, we may share Personal Information supplied by the User with Affiliate Members. These Affiliate Members will not use this Personally Identifiable Information other than for the express purpose of providing the service(s) requested. For example, when Users purchaser paid service from **W3links.net** , we provide user's email address and other personal information to our authorized retailer to process their order and verify fraud related activities.

**No Liability for Acts of Third Parties.**  
Although these websites will use commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of Personal Information and/or the registration data, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. **W3links.net** will have no liability for disclosure of registration data due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.  
**  
Use of Aggregated Information.**  
**W3links.net** reserves the right to disclose to third parties information about Users usage of the Site and any related services, including information gathered during use of the Site by Users. Any information disclosed will be in aggregate data form (such as overall patterns or demographic reports) that does not describe or identify any individual User.

**Access to Personal Information.**  
Upon request via e-mail to info@W3links.net with the subject "Access to Personal Information", **W3links.net** will provide Users with a summary of any of their Personal Information retained by these websites. Users may modify, correct, change or update their Personal Information or cause their Personal Information to be removed from the **W3links.net** database. **W3links.net** will only send Personal Information records to the e-mail address on file for the User name associated with it.

**Children's Privacy.  
W3links.net** does not specifically collect information about children, but is concerned about the safety of children and their use of the Internet. Therefore, we will never knowingly request or solicit personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. In the event that we receive actual knowledge that we have collected such personal information without the requisite and verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as is practical.

**Updates.**  
This Privacy Policy is effective as of February 01, 2007. **W3links.net** reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other **W3links.net** policy or practice, at any time with reasonable notice to users of the Site. Any changes or updates will be effective upon posting to the Site. Regardless of any changes we make to our Privacy Policy, we will only use your personal information in accordance with the version of the Privacy Policy in place at the time you provided your information unless you give us your consent to do otherwise. Your continued use of the Site following our posting of a change notice will constitute binding acceptance of those changes for future collections.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us at info@W3links.net.

**W3links.net**

Effective Date: Feb 01, 2007  
  
---|---|---
